[{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Leadership is a process where one individual ________ a group to achieve desired outcomes.",
    "answer": "influences"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The focus of a manager is on stability, control, and ________.",
    "answer": "efficiency"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "The Great Man Theory of Leadership suggests that great leaders are ________, not made.",
    "answer": "born"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Charismatic Leadership focuses on leaders who inspire through their ________ and vision.",
    "answer": "personality"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "According to Trait Theory, effective leaders possess both innate and ________ traits.",
    "answer": "acquired"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Behavioral Theory of Leadership emphasizes actions over ________ traits.",
    "answer": "inherent"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The Ohio State University identified two critical leadership behaviors: Initiating Structure and ________.",
    "answer": "Consideration"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "According to Charismatic Leadership, bold actions that demonstrate commitment are called ________ behavior.",
    "answer": "personal risk-taking"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The ________ Theory suggests that the effectiveness of leadership depends on the fit between the leaderâ€™s style and situational demands.",
    "answer": "Contingency"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Effective leaders who balance production and morale are considered ________ leaders.",
    "answer": "Employee-Centered"
  }
]
